Guide to the Alvin A. Achenbaum Papers, 1948-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Files, 1949-2011 and undated
  - Audiovisual Materials
    - Miller High Life 1984 presentation (Powerpoint) on CD-R. 2003. (Box 25)
    - Neostem Adult Stem Cell Documentary. DVD. 2007. (Box 25)
    - Wachter Productions demonstration. DVD. Undated. (Box 25)
- Achenbaum Associates, 1984-2000 and undated
  - Account Files
    - American Red Cross
      - Atlanta Chapter public opinion survey, 1992 (Box AA1)
      - Bay Area focus group, 1993 (Box AA1)
      - Benefit optimization research, 1992 (Box AA1)
      - Corporate Perceptions of the St. Louis Bi-State Chapter, 1993 (Box AA1)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1994 (Box AA1)
      - Database-Driven Fundraising, 1994 (Box AA1)
      - Fact Book, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box AA1)
      - Greater Minneapolis Area Chapter awareness and attitude studies, 1991 (Box AA1)
      - Homeless, 1986-1993 (Box AA1)
      - In-Depth Interviews with Opinion Leaders/Influentials, 1993 (Box AA1)
      - Insiders Discuss Support for Charitable Organizations, 1993 (Box AA1)
      - January meeting, 1994 (Box AA2)
      - Marketing plan, 1993-1995, (2 folders) (Box AA2)
      - Non-donor survey/Donor survey, 1992 (Box AA2)
      - Northern California Earthquake Preparedness Study, 1991 (Box AA2)
      - Oregon Trail Chapter, Community Image Assessment, 1991 (Box AA2)
      - Penetration of the American Red Cross among the General Public, 1993 (Box AA2)
      - Proposals, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box AA2)
      - Public and donor perceptions in the Greater New York area, 1990 (Box AA2)
      - Recommendation, 1995 (Box AA2)
      - Red Cross/GNY Image Survey, 1993 (Box AA2)
      - Review of 1993 Financial Statements, 1993 (Box AA3)
      - Southeastern Michigan Chapter image and awareness study, 1991 (Box AA3)
      - Southeastern Pennsylvania Chapter Community Needs/Awareness/Involvement, 1989 (Box AA3)
      - Southeastern Pennsylvania Chapter major donor study, 1993 (Box AA3)
      - Study among ARC Volunteers, 1994 (Box AA3)
      - Study among Donors to Charitable Organizations, 1994 (Box AA3)
      - Things to read, 1994 (Box AA3)
      - United Way research and data, 1993 (Box AA3)
      - Volunteer 2000 study, 1988 (Box AA3)
      - Wirthin/Gallop research, 1991 (Box AA3)
      - Yankelovich Monitor, 1993 (Box AA4)
      - Yankelovich presentation, 1993 (Box AA4)
      - Yankelovich study, 1993 (Box AA4)
    - Armstrong Air Conditioning/Lennox
      - ACT (Armstrong Challenging Tomorrow), 1994 (Box AA4)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1994 (Box AA4)
      - Presentations, 1994 (Box AA4)
    - Baybanks
      - Agency search, 1993 (Box AA4)
    - Bell Atlantic
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1993-1995 (Box AA4)
      - Interactive television, 1993 (Box AA4)
      - Request for proposal on assisting agency search, 1995 (Box AA4)
      - Comedy Central (Box AA4)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1993 (Box AA5)
    - Conagra
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1993 (Box AA5)
    - H&R Block
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995 (Box AA5)
    - Hallmark Cards
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1988 (Box AA5)
    - Honda
      - Agency/client agreement, 1993 (Box AA5)
      - Agency fees and media consolidation, 1993 (Box AA5)
      - Agency/partnership review (Rubin Postaer), 1987 (Box AA5)
      - Analysis and presentation on competition, 1992 (Box AA5)
      - Compensation, 1984-1987 (Box AA5)
      - Financial discussions to date, 1993 (Box AA5)
      - Marketing plan, 1993 (Box AA5)
      - Presentations, circa 1993 (Box AA5)
    - Hunt-Wesson
      - Letters to Branch Watkins, undated (Box AA6)
    - Integrity Music
      - Research, 1994 (Box AA6)
    - Kayser-Roth (litigation with Sara Lee)
      - 2nd and 3rd affidavits of James Fouss, 1993 (Box AA6)
      - Affidavits, 1989, (3 folders) (Box AA6)
      - Attorney work product, 1993 (Box AA6)
      - Consumer Perceptions of Sheer Energy, 1993 (Box AA6)
      - Consumer Perceptions of Leg Looks and Jaclyn Smith, 1993 (Box AA6)
      - Defendants' brief, 1993, (1 of 6 folders) (Box AA6)
      - Defendants' brief, 1993, (2-6 of 6 folders) (Box AA7)
      - Exhibits, 1993, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box AA7)
      - Exhibits, 1993, (3 of 3 folders) (Box AA8)
      - Exhibits for motion, 1993, (4 folders) (Box AA8)
      - Final judgment, 1994 (Box AA8)
      - James Fouss, direct examination, 1993, (2 folders) (Box AA8)
      - Smith Helms Mulliss & Moore, 1993 (Box AA8)
      - Thomas DuPont testimony, 1993 (Box AA9)
    - K-Mart
      - Agency search, 1994-1995 (Box AA9)
      - Compensation, 1994-1996 (Box AA9)
      - Contracts with Campbell Mithun Esty, 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box AA9)
    - Lexus/Toyota
      - Agency review, 1993 (Box AA9)
    - McNeil
      - Tylenol PM, 1995 (Box AA9)
    - Minolta
      - Advertising Review Committee meeting, 1994 (Box AA9)
      - Lois problem, 1994 (Box AA9)
      - Photo Division planning meeting, 1994 (Box AA9)
      - Position papers, 1994 (Box AA10)
    - Multiple Sclerosis Society
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2000 (Box AA10)
    - Muppets
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995 (Box AA10)
    - Nestlé
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1993 (Box AA10)
    - Quaker Oats
      - Advertising, 1993 (Box AA10)
      - Agency review, 1993 (Box AA10)
      - Brand shifting and buyer analysis, 1993 (Box AA10)
      - Cereal category report, 1993 (Box AA10)
      - Consumer Health Habits (M/A/R/C), 1993 (Box AA10)
      - Data summary, 1994 (Box AA10)
      - Market analysis, 1993 (Box AA10)
      - Market report, 1993 (Box AA10)
      - Memorandum and Key Learning, 1993 (Box AA10)
      - Research, 1993 (Box AA11)
      - Situation analysis, 1993 (Box AA11)
    - Romance Classics
      - Agency selection, 1994 (Box AA11)
    - Seagram
      - Absolut Kurant, 1994, (2 folders) (Box AA11)
      - Agency search, 1994 (Box AA11)
      - Assessment of Advertising Agency Services, 1985 (Box AA11)
      - Captain Morgan general market conclusions, 1994 (Box AA11)
      - Captain Morgan market and brand asset review, 1994 (Box AA11)
      - Captain Morgan presentation, 1994 (Box AA12)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1994 (Box AA12)
      - Evolutionary Advertising Research, 1992, (2 folders) (Box AA12)
      - Presentations, 1994 (Box AA12)
      - Restoring Luster to Tarnished Brands, 1994 (Box AA12)
      - Rum attitude and usage, 1994, (3 folders) (Box AA12)
      - Slide show, 1991 (Box AA13)
    - Tropicana
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box AA13)
  - General Files
    - Acquiring WPP's market research business, 1993 (Box AA14)
    - Awards letters and designs, 1993 (Box AA14)
    - Brand Asset Based Strategic Marketing Planning (M/A/R/C), undated (Box AA14)
    - Charities, 1990-1994, (2 folders) (Box AA14)
    - Competitor--Wanamaker, 1991-1999 (Box AA14)
    - Competitors, 1994 and undated (Box AA14)
    - Conflict insurance, 1987-1995 (Box AA14)
    - Davis & Gilbert, 1993 (Box AA14)
    - Evaluation forms and miscellaneous, 1994 (Box AA14)
    - Interactive television and the Internet, 1993, (2 folders) (Box AA14)
    - M/A/R/C TargetBase, 1993 (Box AA15)
    - Obtaining New Business, 1995 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AA15)
    - Peter Krausher, 1995 (Box AA15)
    - Telecommunications, 1996 (Box AA15)
    - WPP annual report, 1990 (Box AA15)
    - WPP market research businesses, 1992-1993, (3 folders) (Box AA15)
- Achenbaum Bogda Associates, 1971-2009 and undated
  - Account Files
    - 7-Eleven
      - Agency assessment, 2005 (Box AB1)
      - Agency presentations, 2004 (Box AB1)
      - Agency relationship management, 2004 (Box AB1)
      - Annual report, 2003 (Box AB1)
      - Fresh Look at TPN, 2004 (Box AB1)
      - Project ABA, 2004 (Box AB1)
      - Printed material, undated (Box AB1)
      - Proposal, 2003-2004 (Box AB1)
      - Tracy Locke, 2004 (Box AB1)
    - America West Airlines
      - Agency review, 1997 (Box AB2)
      - Agency search, 1997 (Box AB2)
      - Compensation, 1997 (Box AB2)
    - American Home Products
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2000 (Box AB2)
    - American Movie Classics
      - Agency review, 1994-1997 (Box AB2)
      - Agency search, 1994 (Box AB2)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1994 (Box AB2)
    - American Red Cross
      - Agency Selection Committee, 2003 (Box AB2)
      - Annual report, 2002 (Box AB3)
      - Attitude cluster analysis, 2003 (Box AB3)
      - Audit status report, 2003 (Box AB3)
      - Blood advertising, 2004 (Box AB3)
      - Building Relationships, 2004 (Box AB3)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2003-2004, (2 folders) (Box AB3)
      - Development, 2004 (Box AB3)
      - EKG advertisements, 2004 (Box AB3)
      - General and Hispanic markets, 2004 (Box AB3)
      - Market situation analysis, 2003, (2 folders) (Box AB3)
      - Media strategy, 2004 (Box AB3)
      - New Generation initiative, 2004, (2 folders) (Box AB4)
      - New Generation outreach, 2003 (Box AB4)
      - ORC study, 2003 (Box AB4)
      - Philanthropy, 2003 (Box AB4)
      - Research, undated (Box AB4)
      - Services contract, 2003 (Box AB4)
      - Strategic research, undated, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box AB4)
      - Strategic research, undated, (3-4 of 4 folders (Box AB5)
      - Synovate draft report, 2003 (Box AB5)
    - Annheuser-Busch
      - Beer industry overview, 2003 (Box AB5)
    - AT&T
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1989 (Box AB5)
    - Campbell Soup
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1996 (Box AB5)
    - City of Addison (Tex.)
      - M/A/R/C research, 1995 (Box AB5)
    - City of Richardson (Tex.)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1998 (Box AB5)
    - Clorox
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995 (Box AB5)
    - Coca-Cola
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2000-2003 (Box AB5)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2004 (Box AB6)
      - Foods trademark analysis, 1994 (Box AB6)
    - Colgate-Palmolive
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1999 (Box AB6)
      - Marketing plans, 1996 (Box AB6)
      - Proposal for Preparing Brand Asset Based Marketing Plans, 1996 (Box AB6)
    - Comedy Central
      - Meetings, 1993, (2 folders) (Box AB6)
    - Dairy Queen
      - Advertising agency agreement, 1972-1997, (2 folders) (Box AB6)
      - Agency interviews, 2000 (Box AB7)
      - Blizzard promotion, 1998 (Box AB7)
      - Child Research Services, Report on a Character Evaluation (Dennis the Menace as potential spokes character), 1993 (Box AB7)
      - Complaint (franchise antitrust suit), 1993 (Box AB7)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995 and undated (Box AB7)
      - Litigation--Plaintiffs, 1999 and undated (Box AB7)
      - Livengood letter, 1997 (Box AB7)
      - Meetings, 1971-1996 (Box AB7)
      - Members, 1978-1997 (Box AB7)
      - Mooty affidavit, 1995 (Box AB7)
      - Reilly et al, 1999 (Box AB7)
    - Deloitte Consulting
      - Agency review, 2000 (Box AB7)
    - Emrys
      - Wireless business application, undated (Box AB7)
    - Ford
      - A.C.E. Insurance vs. Ford arbitration, 1999 (Box AB7)
      - Ford vs. A.C.E. exhibit binder, 1998, (3 folders) (Box AB8)
      - Pile and Co., SUV safety study, 2003 (Box AB8)
    - Franklin Mint
      - Advertising for Princess Diana products, 1999, (3 folders) (Box AB8)
      - Bradford Exchange, 1997-2000 (Box AB9)
      - Declaration of witnesses, 2000, (4 folders) (Box AB9)
      - Defendants' Answer and Defenses to Plaintiffs' Second Amended Complaint, 1999 (Box AB9)
      - Depositions, 1999-2000, (1-3 of 9 folders) (Box AB9)
      - Depositions, 1999-2000, (4-9 of 9 folders) (Box AB10)
      - Loeb & Loeb correspondence, 1986-2000 (Box AB10)
      - Notes on use of Princess Diana's name and likeness, undated (Box AB10)
      - Order Granting in Part and Denying in Part Defendants' Motion to Dismiss, 1998 (Box AB10)
      - Request for Judicial Notice, 2000, (1 of 3 folders) (Box AB10)
      - Request for Judicial Notice, 2000, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box AB11)
      - Second Amended Complaint, 1999 (Box AB11)
    - Frito-Lay
      - notes, undated (Box AB11)
    - General Motors
      - Compensation assessment, 2002 (Box AB11)
      - Marketing and Advertising Service Agreement, 2002 (Box AB11)
      - Quantitative Business Management, 2001 (Box AB11)
    - Glaxo
      - Proposals, 2001 (Box AB11)
    - Golden Corral
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2000 (Box AB11)
    - Goodmark Foods
      - Agency review, 1999 (Box AB11)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1999 (Box AB11)
    - GTE
      - Accountabilities, 1997 (Box AB12)
      - Advertising binder, 1995, (2 folders) (Box AB12)
      - Advertising effectiveness research, 1997 (Box AB12)
      - Agency compensation, 1994 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AB12)
      - Agency credentials meeting, 1996 (Box AB12)
      - Agency review, 1995-1996, (1-3 of 6 folders) (Box AB12)
      - Agency review, 1995-1996, (4-6 of 6 folders) (Box AB13)
      - Agency transition, 1997 (Box AB13)
      - Airfone, 1997 (Box AB13)
      - Answer Man receiver reaction, 1996 (Box AB13)
      - Brand campaign, 1996 (Box AB13)
      - Brand council/schedule, 1996 (Box AB13)
      - Brand proposal, 1997 (Box AB13)
      - Branding project, 1995 (Box AB13)
      - Business segmentation, undated (Box AB14)
      - Catalog receiver reaction, 1997 (Box AB14)
      - Compensation, 2000 (Box AB14)
      - Compensation position paper, 1996 (Box AB14)
      - Consumer loyalty program, 1997 (Box AB14)
      - Contract, 1999 (Box AB14)
      - Contract with Temerlin McClain, 1999 (Box AB14)
      - Custom cards, 1997 (Box AB14)
      - Customer retention, 1997 (Box AB14)
      - Customer satisfaction, 1996 (Box AB14)
      - Digital media advertising agencies, 1996 (Box AB14)
      - Final contract, 1997 (Box AB14)
      - Focus, 1997 (Box AB14)
      - Glen Gilbert, 1997, (2 folders) (Box AB14)
      - High value customer retention, 1997 (Box AB15)
      - High value customers, 1997 (Box AB15)
      - Interviews, 1996 (Box AB15)
      - Invitation to credentials meeting, 1996 (Box AB15)
      - Leadership 2000, undated (Box AB15)
      - Letter of commendation, 1997 (Box AB15)
      - Lippincott & Margulies, 1996 (Box AB15)
      - Market study, 1996, (2 folders) (Box AB15)
      - Market study--cellular business, 1996 (Box AB15)
      - Marketing, 1997 (Box AB15)
      - Master agreement with Temerlin, 1998 (Box AB15)
      - Measuring Impact, 1997 (Box AB16)
      - Meeting with Ogilvy & Mather, 1997 (Box AB16)
      - Mobilnet and CLOB segmentation, 1996 (Box AB16)
      - Monitoring the agreement and profit protection, 1997 (Box AB16)
      - Ogilvy & Mather contract, 1999 (Box AB16)
      - Ogilvy One: Direct marketing, 2000 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AB16)
      - Ogilvy strategy, 1997 (Box AB16)
      - Orientation, 1997 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AB16)
      - Positioning GTE for the Millennium, 1994 (Box AB16)
      - Request for position papers, 1996 (Box AB16)
      - Residential ATP, 1996, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box AB16)
      - Residential ATP, 1996, (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box AB17)
      - Segmentation research, undated (Box AB17)
      - Staffing and compensation, undated (Box AB17)
      - Strategic Market Opportunities for GTE CLOB, 1995 (Box AB17)
      - Subscription pricing, 1997 (Box AB17)
      - Summary material, 1997 (Box AB17)
      - System/Value Marketing Plan, 1997 (Box AB17)
      - TargetBase Marketing, 1997 (Box AB17)
      - Telemarketing plan, 1997 (Box AB17)
      - Telephone operations, 1995 (Box AB18)
      - Telops agency search, 1996, (2 folders) (Box AB18)
      - Telops direct marketing, 1996 (Box AB18)
      - Temerlin, 1997 (Box AB18)
      - Top five priorities, 1997 (Box AB18)
      - Vertical Leap '97, 1996 (Box AB18)
    - Hallmark Cards
      - Agency review, 2007 (Box AB18)
      - Billing, 2007 (Box AB18)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box AB18)
    - Hanes
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2001 (Box AB18)
    - Heatcraft Refrigeration Products
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2004 (Box AB18)
    - Heinz
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995 (Box AB19)
      - Promotion, 1994 (Box AB19)
    - HMS Partners
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1998 (Box AB19)
    - Hyundai
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1987-1997 (Box AB19)
    - Integrity Music
      - Animated video, 1996, (2 folders) (Box AB19)
      - Annual report, 1994-1996 (Box AB19)
      - Branding, 1996 (Box AB19)
      - Branding guidelines, undated (Box AB19)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1993 (Box AB19)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1996 and undated (Box AB20)
      - Direct mail tests, 1996 (Box AB20)
      - Direct Response Problem, 1996 (Box AB20)
      - Direct sales force, 1995 (Box AB20)
      - Industry and company report, 1995 (Box AB20)
      - Integrity and Its Brands, 1996 (Box AB20)
      - Music Purchasing from Record Clubs and Retail Outlets, 1995 (Box AB20)
      - Negative option, 1996, (2 folders) (Box AB20)
      - New product development--High King animation series (questionnaire), undated (Box AB20)
      - Notes, interviews, 1995, (2 folders) (Box AB20)
      - Plan outlines, 1995 (Box AB20)
      - Printed material, 1996 and undated (Box AB21)
      - Proposal, 1994 (Box AB21)
      - Strategy review, 1996 (Box AB21)
      - Television, 1996 (Box AB21)
      - Work session, 1995 (Box AB21)
    - Kia
      - ABA response, 2004 (Box AB21)
      - Agency search, 2004, (2 folders) (Box AB21)
      - Agreement with David & Goliath, 2003 (Box AB21)
      - Compensation analysis, 2004 (Box AB21)
      - Cramer-Kasselt presentation, undated (Box AB21)
      - David & Goliath response, 2004 (Box AB21)
      - Finalist meetings, 2004, (2 folders) (Box AB21)
      - GSD&M creative presentation, 2004 (Box AB22)
      - GSD&M Purpose Based Branding, 2004 (Box AB22)
      - GSD&M response, 2004 (Box AB22)
      - Kirshenbaum Bond position papers, 2004 (Box AB22)
      - Search evaluation, 2004 (Box AB22)
    - K-Mart
      - Agency search, 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box AB22)
      - Agency selection, 1995, (2 folders) (Box AB22)
      - Campbell Mithun Esty agency fact sheet, 1994 (Box AB22)
      - Campbell Mithun Esty Big Red One and 1994 overview, 1994 (Box AB22)
      - Compensation, 1996 (Box AB22)
      - Consumer tracking study, 1993 (Box AB23)
      - Fashion Focus series, 1994 (Box AB23)
      - K-Mart and CME, 1995 (Box AB23)
      - Pro-forma contracts, 1995-1996 (Box AB23)
      - Proposals, 1995 (Box AB23)
      - Turnaround strategy, 1995 (Box AB23)
    - Krispy Kreme
      - Notes and clippings, 1999 (Box AB23)
    - Lennox
      - Advertising agency compensation review, 1999 (Box AB23)
      - Advertising Council, 2002 (Box AB23)
      - American Residential Services annual report, 1997 (Box AB23)
      - Armstrong AC
        - Dealer research, 2003 (Box AB23)
        - Distribution, 2003 (Box AB23)
        - Lower Third Tier Market, undated (Box AB23)
        - Market assessment, 1995, (2 folders) (Box AB23)
        - Research, 1998 (Box AB24)
        - Situation analysis, 2003 (Box AB24)
        - Strategic branding plan, 1998 (Box AB24)
        - Strategy, 1998 (Box AB24)
        - Big Box Retail Outlet Study, 2001 (Box AB24)
      - Commercial Business Unit
        - Assessment, undated (Box AB24)
        - Market situation analysis, 2004 (Box AB24)
        - Participant research, circa 2004 (Box AB24)
        - Research, 2004 and undated, (3 folders) (Box AB24)
        - Situation analysis, 2004 (Box AB24)
        - Consolidation initiative, 2003 (Box AB25)
        - Consumer tracking study, 2001 (Box AB25)
        - Co-operative advertising, 2001-2003 (Box AB25)
        - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1994-2004 (Box AB25)
        - Florida agency search, 2003 (Box AB25)
        - Florida initiative, 2002, (2 folders) (Box AB25)
        - Forecast evaluation, undated (Box AB25)
        - Home Depot, 2000 (Box AB25)
        - Leading the Way in HVAC, undated (Box AB25)
        - Market assessment, 1994 (Box AB25)
        - Market planning worksession, 1997 (Box AB25)
        - Market situation analysis, circa 2004 (Box AB25)
        - NARP marketing initiative, 2002 (Box AB25)
        - NARP second tier assessment, 2002 (Box AB26)
        - NARP surveys, 2002 (Box AB26)
        - New economy, 2001 (Box AB26)
        - Notes on consolidation, 1998 (Box AB26)
        - Problems and opportunities, undated (Box AB26)
        - Profile of HVAC retail experts, 1997 (Box AB26)
        - Request for proposal, 2003 (Box AB26)
        - Research on Lennox commercial business, undated (Box AB26)
        - Review of pricing and communications issues, 2002 (Box AB26)
        - Sears, 2000-2001, (2 folders) (Box AB26)
      - Service Experts
        - Advanced Vision Team, 2004 (Box AB26)
        - Annual report, 1997-1998 (Box AB26)
        - Compensation, 2001 (Box AB26)
        - Greater Toronto Area District Strategic Plan, 2001 (Box AB26)
        - Trademark assessment, 2004 (Box AB26)
        - Vision statements, 2004 and undated (Box AB27)
        - Vision Task Force, 2004 (Box AB27)
        - Situation analysis, 2004 (Box AB27)
        - Strategic marketing plan, 1997, (2 folders) (Box AB27)
    - Lockheed Martin
      - Agency search, 2001 (Box AB27)
    - Mattel
      - Notice of annual meeting, 2003 (Box AB27)
    - Mead Johnson
      - Analysis of the Nutrition Market (M/A/R/C), 1994 (Box AB27)
    - Miller Brewing Company
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2003 and undated (Box AB28)
      - Presentation, undated (Box AB28)
      - South African Breweries, 2002-2003 and undated (Box AB28)
    - Nationwide
      - Agency compensation, 2002, (4 folders) (Box AB28)
      - Agency review, 1997, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box AB28)
      - Agency review, 1997, (3 of 3 folders) (Box AB29)
      - Agency search, 1997 (Box AB29)
      - Agency selection finalist meetings, 1997 (Box AB29)
      - Annual report, 1996-2000, (2 folders) (Box AB29)
      - Assignment, 2001 (Box AB29)
      - Brand idea, 1997 (Box AB29)
      - Brand strategy, 1997 (Box AB29)
      - Branding, 1997 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AB29)
      - Business Unit strategic plans, 2001 (Box AB29)
      - Campbell Mithun Esty position papers, 1997 (Box AB29)
      - Compensation, 1997 (Box AB30)
      - Corporate strategy, 2001 (Box AB30)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1998-2003, (3 folders) (Box AB30)
      - Economic value, 2001 (Box AB30)
      - Icon Media deal, 2002 (Box AB30)
      - Interim Guidelines--Power of You, 1999 (Box AB30)
      - Ketchum, 1997 (Box AB30)
      - Making Customer Choice a Reality at Nationwide, 2001 (Box AB30)
      - Nationwide Tour/PGA, 2003 (Box AB30)
      - Process for Selecting a New Advertising Agency, undated (Box AB30)
      - Review of the Nationwide Situation, 2001 (Box AB30)
      - Revised Agent Advertising Guide, 2000 (Box AB30)
      - Role of Advertising and the Effectiveness of the Organization, 2001 (Box AB30)
      - Strategic communications plan, 2001 (Box AB30)
      - Temerlin McClain
        - Compensation, 2004, (1 of 2 folders) (Box AB30)
        - Compensation, 2004, (2 of 2 folders) (Box AB31)
        - Contract, 2002 (Box AB31)
        - Interactive Advertising Point of View and Recommendation, 2001 (Box AB31)
        - Media Planning Responsibilities, 2003 (Box AB31)
        - Presentation, 2001 (Box AB31)
        - Reports and miscellaneous, 1997-2001 (Box AB31)
        - Unit Linked Life Insurance Concept Test, 2001 (Box AB31)
        - Urban and Hispanic Advertising Representation, 2001 (Box AB31)